taxpolicycenter.org 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Tax Policy Center

##### **Personal Information**

The Tax Policy Center does not collect personal information about website visitors without their consent. When we request such information to provide a service or respond to an inquiry, visitors need to provide only the minimal information necessary.

##### **How Is Personal Information Used?**

Personal information is used by Tax Policy Center staff only for the purpose stated at the time it is collected—e.g., to reply to a question or inquiry or to provide a requested service. Such personal information is never used for secondary or unrelated purposes unless otherwise requested or explicitly agreed to by the website user.

The Tax Policy Center’s policy is never to share, trade,sell or otherwise disclose personal information to third-parties without the individual's informed consent or direction except where required by law. When requested, and where possible, we will delete personal information from current operational systems.

##### **Use of E-mail Newsletters**

The Tax Policy Center uses e-mail delivery software to send topical newsletters to subscribers. The software may allow us to measure how our newsletter and website are used. We view such data in the aggregate only (and never look at data on individual subscribers). We do not sell or share our e-mail lists, and subscribers may remove themselves at any time.

##### **Use of Server Logs**

The Tax Policy Center web servers log standard information about website users, including the IP address of the user, URLs visited, and the date/time visited. We use this information to generate aggregate reports that summarize our website traffic, which we use to improve our site and make it easier for visitors to use. We do not attempt to track individual users, and we do not link the web log information to any other database.

##### **Use of Cookies**

The Tax Policy Center makes use of very short-lived (24- hour) cookies to assign unique user-session identifications. We do not use cookies for any other purpose; nor is the information stored in the cookies linked to any other data.

##### **Web Bugs**

The Tax Policy Center does not use web bugs (programs installed on your personal computer by a website to track personal web usage).

##### **Links to Third-Party Sites**

The Tax Policy Center provides links to selected third-party sites, but assumes no responsibility for the practices of those websites.
